Guide to the University Of Montana (System) Records 1915-1958
Montana Historical Society
University Of Montana (System) Records
1915-1958
Montana Historical Society Archives
RS 72
University of Montana (System)
22 linear feet of shelf space
These University of Montana System records (1915-1958) consist of general correspondence, subject files, budgetary materials, and scrapbooks from the Chancellor and the Executive Secretary offices.
The University of Montana at Missoula was established in 1893. In 1913 Montana's higher education system was unified under the name University of Montana, and the name of the university at Missoula was changed to State University of Montana. In 1965 the name of the statewide office was changed to Montana University System. Under the system were the University of Montana at Missoula (formerly Montana State University), Montana State University at Bozeman (formerly Montana State College), Western Montana College at Dillon (formerly Montana State Normal School), Eastern Montana College at Billings, and Northern Montana College at Havre.
Records consist of budget materials (1915-1953) for the various segments of the University System; a report (1933) by M.A. Brannon on the history of the University; student registration reports (1921-1927); speeches (1925-1933) by Chancellor M.A. Brannon; subject files (1915-1919) on each segment of the University; a subject file on The Montana Study (1944-1947); conference materials (1928-1957) for the University Executive Council; clippings; and other materials.
The collection is arranged by series.
Collection open for research.
Acquisition information is available upon request.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the Montana Historical Society Archives catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search under these terms.
Brownell, Baker, 1887-1965; Elrod, Morton John, 1863-1953; Hanson, Bert B.; Howard, Joseph Kinsey, 1906-1951; Levine, Louis; Linfield, F. B.; Melby, Ernest O.; Merriam, H. G.; Rowe, J. P.; Robinson, Ruth; Meadows, Paul; Brandborg, G.M.; Smith, Frank; Posten, Richard
Intermountain Union College (Helena, Mont.); United States Army Students' Army Training Corps; Montana Agricultural Experiment Station; Montana Council of Defense; Montana Historical Society; Montana School of Mines; Montana State College; Montana State COllege of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts; Montana State Normal College; Western Montana College of Education; Western Montana College; Montana State University--Bozeman. Extension Service; University of Montana--Missoula; State University of Montana (Missoula, Mont.); Montana State University (Missoula, Mont.); University of Montana (System); United States. Council of National Defense; Rockefeller Foundation; Conference on American Thought (1944: Princeton, NJ)
Agricultural colleges; Agricultural experiment stations; Agricultural extension work; County agricultural agents; Environmental policy; Epidemics; Influenza Epidemic, 1918; Patriotism; Salish Indians; Salish Indians--Government relations; Taxation; Teachers colleges; Theater; Universities and colleges; Vocational education; World War, 1914-1918; Rural conditions; Sociology, Rural
Conrad (Mont.); Darby (Mont.); Flathead Indian Reservation (Mont.); Flathead Lake Bird Reserve (Mont.); Hamilton (Mont.); Havre (Mont.)--politics And Government; Lewistown (Mont.); Libby (Mont.); Lonepine (Mont.); Stevensville (Mont.); Troy (Mont.); Victor (Mont.); Arlee (Mont.); Dixon (Mont.)
Montana
Detailed Description of the Collection
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection
- Financial Records
  - Annual financial reports, 1917-1920 (Box-folder 1 / 1)
  - Budgets: Agricultural College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, University, Normal College, School of Mines, Havre Farm School, Chancellor's Office, 1915-1918 (Box-folder 1 / 2-5)
  - Budgets: report, 1916 (Box-folder 1 / 6)
  - Budgets: University, Normal College, School of Mines, Chancellor's Office, Agricultural College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 1 / 7-8)
  - Budgets: University, State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, Normal College, School of Mines [preliminary], 1917-1919 (Box-folder 2 / 1-4)
  - Budgets: University, Normal College, School of Mines, Chancellor's Office, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 2 / 5)
  - Budgets: State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 3 / 1)
  - Budgets: University, Normal College, School of Mines, Chancellor's Office, State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, 1920-1921 (Box-folder 3 / 2-3)
  - Budgets: University, Normal College, School of Mines, Chancellor's Office, State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, 1921 (Box-folder 3 / 4-5)
  - Budgets estimates: State College, Extension Service, 1921-1923 (Box-folder 3 / 6-7)
  - Budgets: University, Normal College, School of Mines, Chancellor's Office, State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 4 / 1-2)
  - Budgets: University, Normal College, School of Mines, Chancellor's Office, State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 4 / 3-4)
  - Budget estimates [all sections], 1923-1925 (Box-folder 4 / 5)
  - Budgets: University, Normal College, School of Mines, Chancellor's Office, State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 4 / 6-7)
  - Budgets: University, Normal College, School of Mines, Chancellor's Office, State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 5 / 1-2)
  - Budget estimates: all sections, 1925-1927 (Box-folder 5 / 3-5)
  - Budgets: University, Normal College, School of Mines, Chancellor's Office, State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, 1925-1927 (Box-folder 5 / 6-7)
  - Budget estimates: all sections, 1927-1929 (Box-folder 5 / 8-9)
  - Budgets: University, Normal College, School of Mines, Chancellor's Office, State College, Experiment Station, Extension Service, 1927-1929 (Box-folder 6 / 1-2)
  - Budget estimates: University, Experiment Station, Normal College, Eastern Montana College, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 6 / 3)
  - Budgets: University, State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, School of Mines, Normal College, Eastern Montana College, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 6 / 4-5)
  - Budget estimates: State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, 1931-1933 (Box-folder 6 / 6-7)
  - Budgets: University, State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, Normal College, School of Mines, Eastern Montana College, 1931-1933 (Box-folder 7 / 1-5)
  - Budget estimates: State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, Northern Montana College, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 7 / 6-7)
  - Budgets: University, State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, Normal College, School of Mines, Northern Montana College, Eastern Montana College, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 7 / 8-11)
  - Budget estimates: University, State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, Northern Montana College, School of Mines, Eastern Montana College, Normal College, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 7 / 12)
  - Budgets: University, State College, Experiment Station, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 7 / 13-14)
  - Budgets: University, State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, Northern Montana College, School of Mines, Eastern Montana College, Normal College, 1937-1945 (Box-folder 8 / 1-10)
  - Budget estimates: University, State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, Northern Montana College, School of Mines, Eastern Montana College, Normal College, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 8 / 11)
  - Budgets: University, State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, Northern Montana College, School of Mines, Eastern Montana College, Normal College, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 9 / 1-5)
  - Budget estimates: University, State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, Northern Montana College, School of Mines, Eastern Montana College, Normal College, 1948-1950 (Box-folder 9 / 6)
  - Budgets: University, State College, Extension Service, Experiment Station, Northern Montana College, School of Mines, Eastern Montana College, Normal College, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 9 / 7)
  - Budget summaries: [entire system], 1915-1922 (Volume Vol. 1)
- Legal Documents
  - Deeds and leases, 1917-1946 (Box-folder 9 / 8)
- Reports
  - Melvin A. Brannon, "Summarizing some of the achievements written into the history of the University of Montana during the ten and a half years of my administration", 1933 (Box-folder 9 / 9)
  - M.J. Elrod, "Report of Park Naturalist, Glacier National Park", 1927 (Box-folder 9 / 10)
  - F.B. Linfield, "Report on trip to Australia and New Zealand", 1932 (Box-folder 9 / 11)
  - Student registration reports: University, 1921-1927 (Box-folder 9 / 12-14)
  - Student registration reports: State College, 1921-1927 (Box-folder 9 / 15-17)
  - Student registration reports: School of Mines, 1921-1927 (Box-folder 10 / 1-2)
  - Student registration reports: Normal College, 1921-1927 (Box-folder 10 / 3-5)
  - Student registration reports: regional summer schools, 1923, 1927 (Box-folder 10 / 6)
  - University System building program, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 10 / 7)
- Speeches
  - Chancellor Melvin A. Brannon (re educational issues, eugenics, prohibition, social evolution, aquatic biology, Montana Bar Association, college athletics, enrichment of rural life, internationalism, etc.), 1925-1933 (Box-folder 10 / 8-9)
- Subject Files
  - Acceptances of appointment [all sections of University], 1916-1918 (Box-folder 10 / 10-15)
  - Administrative memoranda index, 1916-1919 (Box-folder 10 / 16)
  - Administrative memoranda, #1-166 [vol. 1-4], 1916-1922 (Box-folder 10 / 17-20)
  - Agricultural College (advertising and publicity), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 10 / 21)
  - Agricultural College (appointments, resignations, leaves of absence), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 10 / 22)
  - Agricultural College (budgets and financial reports), 1915-1918 (Box-folder 10 / 23)
  - Agricultural College (buildings), 1915-1918 (Box-folder 10 / 24)
  - Agricultural College (calendar), 1919 (Box-folder 10 / 25)
  - Agricultural College (chemistry building fire), 1916 (Box-folder 10 / 26)
  - Agricultural College (committees), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 10 / 27)
  - Agricultural College (credits and degrees), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 10 / 28)
  - Agricultural College (Dean of Women), 1918 (Box-folder 10 / 29)
  - Agricultural College (dormitories), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 10 / 30)
  - Agricultural College (endowments), 1917 (Box-folder 10 / 31)
  - Agricultural College (Engineering Dept.), 1915-1918 (Box-folder 10 / 32)
  - Agricultural College (enrollment), 1915-1918 (Box-folder 10 / 33)
  - Agricultural College (equipment and supplies), 1918 (Box-folder 10 / 34)
  - Agricultural College (freshmen standings), 1919 (Box-folder 10 / 35)
  - Agricultural College (German Dept.), 1918 (Box-folder 10 / 36)
  - Agricultural College (Home Economics Dept.), 1919 (Box-folder 11 / 1)
  - Agricultural College (influenza epidemic), 1918 (Box-folder 11 / 2)
  - Agricultural College (lands and land improvements), 1915-1919 (Box-folder 11 / 3)
  - Agricultural College (library), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 11 / 4)
  - Agricultural College (Military Dept.), 1915-1919 (Box-folder 11 / 5)
  - Agricultural College (Music Dept.), 1918 (Box-folder 11 / 6)
  - Agricultural College (news notes), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 11 / 7)
  - Agricultural College (newspaper clippings), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 11 / 8)
  - Agricultural College (nurses' training), 1918 (Box-folder 11 / 9)
  - Agricultural College (pavement), 1918 (Box-folder 11 / 10)
  - Agricultural College (payroll and salaries), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 11 / 11)
  - Agricultural College (reports of president, etc.), 1914-1915 (Box-folder 11 / 12)
  - Agricultural College (secondary education), 1916 (Box-folder 11 / 13)
  - Agricultural College (State Historical Library), 1917 (Box-folder 11 / 14)
  - Agricultural College (student activity fees), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 11 / 15)
  - Agricultural College (Student Army Training Corps), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 11 / 16-17)
  - Agricultural College (summer school), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 11 / 18)
  - Agricultural College (travel reports), 1919 (Box-folder 11 / 19)
  - Agricultural College (vocational education), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 11 / 20)
  - Blank diplomas, undated (Box-folder 11 / 21)
  - Blank forms, undated (Box-folder 11 / 22)
  - Experiment Station, 1912-1921 (Box-folder 11 / 23)
  - Experiment Station (accounts), 1918 (Box-folder 11 / 24)
  - Experiment Station (agreements), 1907-1917 (Box-folder 11 / 25)
  - Experiment Station (Dairy Commissioner), 1917 (Box-folder 11 / 26)
  - Experiment Station (dehydration of fruits and vegetables), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 11 / 27)
  - Experiment Station (Director F.B. Linfield loyalty issue), 1917 (Box-folder 11 / 28)
  - Experiment Station (financial reports), 1912-1917 (Box-folder 11 / 29)
  - Experiment Station (Grain Laboratory), 1917 (Box-folder 11 / 30)
  - Experiment Station (payrolls), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 11 / 31)
  - Experiment Station (reports of director), 1914-1915 (Box-folder 11 / 32)
  - Experiment Station (substations: Huntley, Judith Basin, Northern Montana, Ronan), 1914-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 1-4)
  - Extension Service, 1916-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 5)
  - Extension Service (appointments), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 6)
  - Extension Service (boys' and girls' clubs), undated (Box-folder 12 / 7)
  - Extension Service (budgets and financial reports), 1914-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 8)
  - Extension Service (county agents), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 9)
  - Extension Service (Extension Workers' Council), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 10)
  - Extension Service (Farm Bureau), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 11)
  - Extension Service (Farmers' Institute), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 12)
  - Extension Service (Field Agent in Marketing), 1918 (Box-folder 12 / 13)
  - Extension Service (Home Demonstration agents), 1918 (Box-folder 12 / 14)
  - Extension Service (land leases), 1917 (Box-folder 12 / 15)
  - Extension Service (Miles City controversy), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 16)
  - Extension Service (payrolls), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 17)
  - Extension Service (project agreements), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 18)
  - Extension Service (projects: marketing), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 19)
  - Extension Service (reports of director), 1916-1917 (Box-folder 12 / 20)
  - Extension Service (seed lien law), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 21)
  - Extension Service (Socialist activities), 1918 (Box-folder 12 / 22)
  - Extension Service (survey), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 23)
  - Farm School at Havre, 1916 (Box-folder 12 / 24)
  - Fort Assiniboine school land, 1915 (Box-folder 12 / 25)
  - Legislation (Board of Control), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 26)
  - Legislation (Bureau of Mines and Metallurgy), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 27)
  - Legislation (Certified Public Accountants), 1917 (Box-folder 12 / 28)
  - Legislation (Chancellorship), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 29)
  - Legislation (cooperative agricultural societies), 1918 (Box-folder 12 / 30)
  - Legislation (Council of Defense), 1917 (Box-folder 12 / 31)
  - Legislation (county extension agents), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 32)
  - Legislation (Farm Bureau), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 33)
  - Legislation (Flathead Lake Bird Reserve), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 34)
  - Legislation (geological survey), 1917 (Box-folder 12 / 35)
  - Legislation (Normal Schools), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 36)
  - Legislation (pharmacy certificates), 1917 (Box-folder 12 / 37)
  - Legislation (physical education), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 38)
  - Legislation (school law), 1917 (Box-folder 12 / 39)
  - Legislation (School of Mines special appropriation), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 40)
  - Legislation (Socialism in the University system), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 41)
  - Legislation (Student Army Training Corps), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 42)
  - Legislation (teacher training in high schools), 1917 (Box-folder 12 / 43)
  - Legislation (University convocation), 1917 (Box-folder 12 / 44)
  - Legislation (Vocational School for Girls), undated (Box-folder 12 / 45)
  - Legislation (miscellaneous), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 46)
  - Memorial of State Universities to Pres. Woodrow Wilson, circa 1915 (Box-folder 12 / 47)
  - Normal College (appointments), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 48)
  - Normal College (budgets and financial reports), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 49)
  - Normal College (commencement), 1917-1920 (Box-folder 12 / 50)
  - Normal College (county superintendents' professional school), 1917 (Box-folder 12 / 51)
  - Normal College (curriculum), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 52)
  - Normal College (dormitories), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 53)
  - Normal College (enrollment), 1918 (Box-folder 12 / 54)
  - Normal College (influenza epidemic), 1918 (Box-folder 12 / 55)
  - Normal College (lands), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 56)
  - Normal College (manual training and art), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 57)
  - Normal College (payrolls and salaries), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 58)
  - Normal College (reports of president), 1914-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 59)
  - Normal College (resignation of President Joseph E. Monroe), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 60)
  - Normal College (training school), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 61)
  - Normal College (travel authorizations), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 12 / 62)
  - Normal College (water rates), 1916-1917 (Box-folder 12 / 63)
  - Normal College (miscellaneous), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 64)
  - Projects and filing systems (indexes), 1917-1920 (Box-folder 12 / 65)
  - Project proposals #101-180, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 66)
  - Project #136 (Congregational Establishment), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 67)
  - Project #143 (Louis Levine, "Taxation of Mines in Montana" and his suspension), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 68-69)
  - Project #164 (University School of Journalism), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 70)
  - Project #166 (University investigation of faculty: primarily Louis Levine and Joseph H. Underwood), 1918 (Box-folder 12 / 71)
  - Project #180 (Inventory of mechanical equipment at Fort Assiniboine), 1919 (Box-folder 12 / 72)
  - School of Mines (appointments), 1918 (Box-folder 13 / 1)
  - School of Mines (budgets and financial reports), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 13 / 2)
  - School of Mines (buildings and grounds), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 3)
  - School of Mines (Bureau of Mines and Metallurgy), 1919 (Box-folder 13 / 4)
  - School of Mines (curriculum), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 5)
  - School of Mines (Experiment Station), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 6)
  - School of Mines (influenza epidemic), 1918 (Box-folder 13 / 7)
  - School of Mines (military instruction and quartering), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 8-9)
  - School of Mines (payrolls), 1919 (Box-folder 13 / 10)
  - School of Mines (President), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 13 / 11)
  - School of Mines (reports of president), 1913-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 12)
  - School of Mines (Student Army Training Corps), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 13-14)
  - School of Mines (travel authorization), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 15)
  - Student Army Training Corps (includes regulations, committee on education and special training, finances), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 16-19)
  - University (appointments and dismissals), 1915-1918 (Box-folder 13 / 20)
  - University (Biological Station), 1916-1918 (Box-folder 13 / 21)
  - University (Botany Dept.), 1918 (Box-folder 13 / 22)
  - University (budgets), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 13 / 23)
  - University (buildings), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 24)
  - University (clippings), 1918 (Box-folder 13 / 25)
  - University (correspondence study fees), 1916-1917 (Box-folder 13 / 26)
  - University (deans of men and women), 1916-1918 (Box-folder 13 / 27)
  - University (Economics Dept.), 1916 (Box-folder 13 / 28)
  - University (Education Dept.), 1916 (Box-folder 13 / 29)
  - University (English Dept.), 1916-1917 (Box-folder 13 / 30)
  - University (enrollment), 1917 (Box-folder 13 / 31)
  - University (filing system), 1918 (Box-folder 13 / 32)
  - University (Forestry School), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 13 / 33)
  - University (general information), 1915 (Box-folder 13 / 34)
  - University (History Dept.), 1917 (Box-folder 13 / 35)
  - University (Home Economics Dept.), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 13 / 36)
  - University (incidental fees), 1916 (Box-folder 13 / 37)
  - University (influenza and scarlet fever epidemics), 1918 (Box-folder 13 / 38)
  - University (Journalism School), 1917 (Box-folder 13 / 39)
  - University (S.C. Kelly controversy), 1916 (Box-folder 13 / 40)
  - University (lands), 1893-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 41)
  - University (Law School, includes fees, Ida W. Dixon bequest), 1913-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 42-44)
  - University (leaves of absence), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 13 / 45)
  - University (N.J. Lennes case), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 13 / 46)
  - University (library), 1916 (Box-folder 13 / 47)
  - University (Library Building Commission, includes minutes and general journal), 1907-1909 (Box-folder 13 / 48-49)
  - University (Military Dept.), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 14 / 1-2)
  - University (Music Building), 1916 (Box-folder 14 / 3)
  - University (news bulletins), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 4)
  - University (newspaper clippings), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 5-7)
  - University (payrolls), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 14 / 8)
  - University (physical education), 1918 (Box-folder 14 / 9)
  - University (President Edward O. Sisson), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 14 / 10)
  - University (Public Service Division), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 11)
  - University (Publications and publicity), 1916-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 12-13)
  - University (repairs and replacements), 1919 (Box-folder 14 / 14)
  - University (reports of president), 1914-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 15)
  - University (J.P. Rowe case), 1917 (Box-folder 14 / 16)
  - University (Scholarship Committee), 1916 (Box-folder 14 / 17)
  - University (staff contracts), 1918 (Box-folder 14 / 18)
  - University (Student Army Training Corps, includes barracks, hospital, Fort Missoula buildings, enrollment, equipment, finances, reports, Section A and Section B), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 14 / 19-26)
  - University (student self government), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 27)
  - University (summer session), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 28)
  - University (supplies), 1918 (Box-folder 14 / 29)
  - University Commission on Montana History, 1917 (Box-folder 14 / 30)
  - Vocational Education, 1916-1920 (Box-folder 14 / 31)
  - Vocational Education Commission (includes reports, correspondence, etc.), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 32-33)
  - War (Reserve Officers' Training Corps), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 14 / 34)
  - #206-5 Agricultural Experiment Station (Cook and Mabee dismissal), 1930 (Box-folder 15 / 1)
  - #207-5 American University Union in Europe, 1919-1924 (Box-folder 15 / 2)
  - #207-5 School of Mines football, 1920 (Box-folder 15 / 3)
  - #209-1 Budget and budget transfers (University), 1919-1921 (Box-folder 15 / 4)
  - #215-7 Conferences (University Executive Council), 1928-1957 (Box-folder 15 / 5-29)
  - #221-1 University School of Forestry, 1919 (Box-folder 15 / 30)
  - #225 Commencements, convocations and public exercises, 1920-1958 (Box-folder 15 / 31-34)
  - #225 convocations and public exercises, 1920-1958 (Box-folder 15 / 33-34)
  - #225 Commencements, convocations, and public exercises (University), 1917-1959 (Box-folder 15 / 35-38)
  - #225 Commencements, convocations, and public exercises (State College), 1920-1958 (Box-folder 15 / 39-42)
  - #225 Commencements, convocations, and public exercises (Normal College), 1920-1953 (Box-folder 16 / 1-3)
  - #225 Commencements, convocations, and public exercises (School of Mines), 1920-1957 (Box-folder 16 / 4-5)
  - #225 Commencements, convocations, and public exercises (Eastern Montana College), 1928-1957 (Box-folder 16 / 6-7)